Rob Grabowski

UX/UI DESIGNFR

rob.j.grabowski@gmail.com (781) 296-7362 robgrabowski.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

ALLEGION, Senior Interaction Designer

May 2022 - Present

Designing a mobile app that interfaces with a physical product.

- Conducted discovery research to understand current product pain points.
- · Created Journey map and Problem Statements to present to stakeholders.
- · Designing wireframes for mobile app.

DIRECT WINES INC., UX/UI Designer

August 2019 - April 2022

- Designed UI to pick up wine at local FedEx, Walgreens, and others.
- Redesigned the checkout flow resulting in a 44% increase in conversions.
- · Redesigned the main navigation for Wall Street Journal Wine (WSJwine).
- Designed a dashboard for wine club members.
- Created react component-based design system with Figma integration.
- · Conducted User Testing with prototypes for all projects.

FACTSET, Senior UX Specialist

March 2019 - July 2019

• Designed a notification system for new apps, research efforts, and system issues.

FACTSET, Interaction Designer

July 2017 - Feb 2019

- · Collaborate with design team on new design standards.
- Present designs to key stakeholders and agile team.
- Designed an onboarding experience for 1000 new users a week.
- Conducted research to understand workflows and validate design ideas.
- Designed message board for investment research notes.
- A team member of FactSet's responsive design effort.

CONSULTANT, Your Private Eyestylist

Jan 2017 - July 2017

- Refined business objectives through a business/brand questionnaire.
- Conducted user surveys to create user personas and user flow diagrams.
- Designed and Developed Responsive Home Page with JavaScript transitions.

FANDISTRO, Director of Business Development April 2011 - June 2016

- Built a business concept from the ground up to an award nomination.
- Co-managed all aspects of the development cycle including UX/UI Design, Quality Assurance, Front End Development, and Database Design.
- Increased signups by over 200% after signup flow analysis and redesign.

ABOUT

I'm a user experience designer and end-user advocate. I solve problems and make websites and mobile apps usable so companies get more value from their customers.

In my free time, I enjoy spending time with my family, exercising, and playing my guitar.

MAIN SKILLS

Figma, Sketch, Axure, Adobe
Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop,
InvisionApp, Agile, JIRA, Balsamiq,
Low/High Fidelity Wireframes &
Mockups, User Surveys, User
Research, User Personas, User Flow
Diagrams, Journey Maps, Problem
Statements, Prototyping, Sitemaps,,
Typeface, Color, Visual Hierarchy,
HTML5, CSS, Javascript, jQuery.

EDUCATION

BLOC

UX/UI Design 2016 - 2017

WEST VIRGINIA UNIVERSITY

B.S., Business Administration, Finance

1990 - 1994

PORTFOLIO

robgrabowski.com